A lunch break – it’s an important and often necessary part of our working or school day.
午休——是我们工作或上学日中重要且通常必不可少的一部分。
It’s a chance to stop your tummy rumbling, grab a bite to eat and maybe chat with some friends.
这是一个让肚子不再咕咕叫、随便吃点东西，或许还能和朋友聊聊天的机会。
And now we’re spoilt with an array of places to buy our lunch from, all offering tempting dishes and humble sandwiches to eat on the go.
如今，我们有各种各样的地方可以买午餐，这些地方都提供诱人的菜肴和简单的三明治，方便我们边走边吃。
But our appetite for buying our lunchtime fare is not just costing us money, there might be a cost in terms of damaging our planet too.
但我们购买午餐不仅花钱，还可能也在破坏我们的地球。
Just grabbing a sandwich, crisps and maybe a cake and coffee can produce at least four items of waste.
仅仅买一份三明治、一包薯片，或许再加一块蛋糕和一杯咖啡，就会产生至少四类垃圾。
Cartons, cups, wrappers and plastic cutlery are all part of our disposable feast in addition to the food waste we create.
除了我们制造的食物垃圾，纸盒、杯子、包装纸和塑料餐具都是这场一次性盛宴的一部分。
Some experts say throwing away food, which produces methane as it rots, is a bigger cause of climate change than plastics.
一些专家表示，食物垃圾腐烂时会产生甲烷，它对气候变化的影响比塑料更大。
But regardless of what causes the most damage, the solution, according to an environmental campaign group called Hubbub, is to eat packed lunches.
但无论哪种因素造成的破坏最大，环保运动组织“喧闹”（Hubbub）表示，解决方案是自带午餐。
Tessa Tricks from the group says "People are saying that they are buying food to take out because life has got busier."
该组织的特莎·特里克说：“人们说他们买外卖是因为生活变得更忙碌了。”
And she says people think they are being more efficient; but she argues that it’s usually healthier and cheaper to make your own lunch.
她还说，人们认为这样更高效，但她认为自己做午餐通常更健康、更便宜。
It means you can eat the things you really want and make the quantity that you actually need.
这意味着你可以吃自己真正想吃的东西，并且做适量的食物。
Of course, preparing your lunch is another thing to fit into your morning scramble of getting ready for work, so if you haven't got time and you are going to buy lunch, an alternative Hubbub suggests is to take your own container to a shop and ask them to put your food in it.
当然，准备午餐是你早上匆忙准备上班时又一件要做的事，所以如果你没时间自己做而要去买午餐，“喧闹”组织建议的另一种选择是自带容器去商店，让店员把食物装进去。
The idea of using reusable coffee cups for hot drinks and refilling water bottles has already proved successful, so this could be another step in the right direction.
使用可重复使用的咖啡杯装热饮和给水瓶加水的想法已经被证明是成功的，所以这可能是朝着正确方向迈出的又一步。
A trial in East Anglia (in the UK) showed that offering a 10% price reduction did persuade some customers to come prepared with their own lunch box.
英国东安格利亚的一项试验表明，提供10%的折扣确实说服了一些顾客自带饭盒。
The problem with eating on the move is that you might want to carry your grub in something that is disposable, so it’s a good idea to make sure it’s something that is recyclable and not to take extra sachets of sauce or utensils that you’re not going to use.
边走边吃的问题在于，你可能想用一次性的东西装食物，所以最好确保它是可回收的，并且不要拿多余的、你不会用的酱料包或餐具。
The message seems to be that if we give our lunchtime eating habits some thought, we can all do our bit in helping reduce climate change and damage to our environment.
这传达的信息似乎是，如果我们多想想自己的午餐习惯，我们都能为减少气候变化和环境破坏出一份力。
That is something for all of us to chew on!
这是值得我们所有人认真思考的事情！